Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers Relating to African American Arts and Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1932–1964; Series IV; 157.31 linear feet
  - Selected Photographic Prints, 12.51 linear feet
    - Photographic Prints
      - Portraits
        - Waters, Ethel, as Hagar in Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1939 February 19; 14 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1969)
          Roll number X o.
          Four prints formerly owned by Grace Nail Johnson.
        - Waters, Ethel, as Petunia Jackson in Cabin in the Sky, musical with music by Vernon Duke, book by Lynn Root, lyrics by John La Touche, and vocal arrangements by Hugh Martin, 1940 November 17; 16 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1970)
          Roll number XVI s.
        - Waters, Ethel, as Petunia Jackson in Cabin in the Sky, musical with music by Vernon Duke, book by Lynn Root, lyrics by John La Touche, and vocal arrangements by Hugh Martin, 1940 November 17; 6 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1971)
        - Waters, Ethel, singing "Stormy Weather" by Harold Arlen and Ted Koehler, 1933 June 22; 14 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1972)
        - Waters, Ethel, singing "Underneath the Harlem Moon" by Mack Gordon and Harry Revel, 1933 June 22; 9 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1973)
        - Waters, Ethel, with a sculpture, Ethel Waters, by Antonio Salemme, 1932 June 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1974)
        - Welch, Elisabeth, 1933 January 19; 11 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1975)
          Includes images of Welch with sculpture, Ethel Waters, 1928, by Antonio Salemme.
        - Welch, Elisabeth, 1946 June 12; 6 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1976)
        - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1951 May 23; 5 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1977)
          Roll number XIII ii.
          Identified by Van Vechten as Dorothy Porter.
        - Wesley, Floyd, Jr., 1941 April 7; 3 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1978)
        - West, Dorothy, 1948 May 17; 6 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1979)
          Roll number XIV ee.
        - Weston, M. Moran, 1961 May 29; 5 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1980)
        - White, Carol Carr, and Josh White, 1946 August 13; 4 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1981)
          Roll number X cc.
        - White, Jane, 1941 September 16; 9 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1982)
        - White, Josh, 1946 August 13; 16 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1983)
        - White, Leah Gladys Powell, 1938 December 30; 11 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1984)
          Roll number XXV n.
        - White, Portia, 1944 December 2; 8 photographic prints (Box 108, Folder 1985)
          Roll number XVIII aa.
        - White, Walter, 1932 August 17; 2 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1986)
        - White, Walter, 1935 January 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1987)
          Roll number XXVI g.
        - White, Walter, 1938 July 12; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1988)
          Roll number XL m.
        - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1938 December 30; 13 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1989)
          Also known as Carl Darrow.
        - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1941 September 16; 6 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1990)
        - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1942 November 29; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1991)
        - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1959 July 14; 7 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1992)
          Roll number XXX: ii.
          Also known as Carl Darrow. Inscriptions on verso of a few prints misidentify the date as July 15, 1959.
        - Wilkins, Roy, 1958 May 27; 8 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1993)
        - Williams, Billy Dee, 1963 January 29; 1 photographic print (Box 109, Folder 1994)
        - Williams, Billy Dee, as The Boy in A Taste of Honey, play by Shelagh Delaney, 1963 January 29; 2 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1995)
        - Williams, Burton, 1961 April 4; 2 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1996)
        - Williams, Camilla, 1946 May 31; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1997)
          Includes images of Williams with a sculpture, Paul Robeson, 1928, by Jacob Epstein.
        - Williams, John A., 1962 July 3; 7 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1998)
        - Williams, Paul R., 1936 March 14; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 1999)
        - Williford, Maurice, 1963 August 28; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2000)
        - Wilson, Ellis, 1948 April 15; 7 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2001)
          Images depict Wilson with examples of his paintings.
        - Wilson, Ellis, 1959 August 12; 3 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2002)
        - Work, Frederick J. (Frederick Jerome), at the home of Albert C. (Albert Coombs) Barnes, Lower Merion Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 February 4; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2003)
        - Work, John W. (John Wesley), at Fisk University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1947 April 26; 3 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2004)
        - Wright, Dale R., 1951 August 3; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2005)
        - Wright, Ellen Poplar, 1945 October 27; 1 photographic print (Box 109, Folder 2006)
          Roll number XIII bb.
        - Wright, Ellen Poplar, and Richard Wright, 1945 October 27; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2007)
        - Wright, Jimmy, 1933 June 26; 6 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2008)
          Identified by Van Vechten as Jimmie Wright.
        - Wright, Jimmy, 1933 November 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2009)
        - Wright, Jimmy, 1939 January 17; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2010)
          Roll number VI o.
        - Wright, Richard, 1939 June 23; 5 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2011)
          Roll number X p.
        - Wright, Richard, 1945 October 27; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2012)
        - Wright, Richard, 1946 March 8; 4 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2013)
        - Wyckoff, William "Stumpy", in This Is the Army, musical with music by Irving Berlin and book by Irving Berlin and James McColl, 1942 August 11; 6 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2014-2015)
        - __________, Marie, the cook for the Pollock family at "The Ship's Rail," the home of Channing Pollock, in Shoreham, New York, 1939 July 15; 3 photographic prints (Box 109, Folder 2016)
          Roll number XIX p.
      - Stage Door Canteen (American Theatre Wing)
        - Archer, Osceola, with Helene Tsang and Victor Wittgenstein, 1943 June 21; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2017)
          Roll number XXII y.
        - Archer, Osceola, with Jimmie Daniels, Marcel Gonthier, Elaine Kent, and Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, 1943 June 21; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2018)
          Roll number XXIV y.
        - Archer, Osceola, with Jimmie Daniels, Marcel Gonthier, Elaine Kent, Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, and Helene Tsang, 1943 June 21; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2019)
        - Archer, Osceola, with Michael Bonifazio, Helene Tsang, and Victor Wittgenstein, 1943 June 21; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2020)
        - Atkinson, Edward, 1943 February 3; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2021)
          Roll number XXI x.
        - Barthé, Richmond, and Coby Ruskin, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2022)
          Roll number XI y.
        - Barthé, Richmond, and Fritzi Scheff, 1943 April 19; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2023)
          Roll number X y.
        - Barthé, Richmond, with Alan Hewitt and Fritzi Scheff, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2024)
        - Battles, Theodore, with LeRoy Feurtado, Bob Moore, Dorothy Randolph Peterson, and Tom Rutherford, 1943 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2025)
          Roll number II z.
        - Battles, Theodore, with LeRoy Feurtado, Dorothy Randolph Peterson, William Raney, and Tom Rutherford, 1943 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2026)
        - Baughman, Cliff, with Robert Carleton and Criton Williams, 1943 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2027)
          Roll number III z.
        - Booth, Shirley, with Harold Jackman, Bob Moore, and Irving Speigel, 1943 August 9; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2028)
        - Carleton, Robert, with Jane White and Criton Williams, 1943 August 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2029)
        - Coburn, Herbert H., with Bobby Evans, Coby Ruskin, and Dorothy Williams, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2030)
        - Coburn, Herbert, with Bobby Evans and Dorothy Fields, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2031)
          Roll number IX y.
        - Coburn, Herbert, with Helen Ford, Langston Hughes, Dorothy Gallagher, Andy Mann, and Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, as well as others obscured in image, 1943 April 8; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2032)
          Roll number VII y.
        - Coburn, Herbert, with Helen Ford, Langston Hughes, Terry Keane, J. H. Keller, and Andy Mann, 1943 April 8; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2033)
          Prints formerly formed part of the Langston Hughes bequest.
        - Crane, Vernon, and Charles Sebree, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2034)
          Roll number XXIV x.
        - Crane, Vernon, and Owen Dodson, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2035)
        - Crane, Vernon, and Owen Dodson, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2036)
          Roll number XXIII x.
        - Crane, Vernon, with Owen Dodson, Allen Porter, and Charles Sebree, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2037)
        - Daniels, Jimmie and Anne Seymour, 1943 June 21; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2038)
        - Denman, Phil, with Owen Dodson, Allen Porter, Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, Charles Sebree, and Don Smith, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2039)
        - Denman, Phil, with Owen Dodson, William Raney, and Hiram Sherman, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2040)
          Roll number XXV x.
        - Dewing, Elizabeth, and Charles Swain, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2041)
        - Dodson, Owen, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2042)
        - Dodson, Owen, 1943 February 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2043)
        - Dodson, Owen, with Saul Mauriber, Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, and Charles Sebree, 1943 February 17; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2044)
        - Evans, Bobby, and Dorothy Fields, 1943 April 19; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2045)
        - Ford, Helen, with Langston Hughes and Terry Keane, 1943 April 8; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2046)
          Roll number VIII y.
        - Hughes, Langston, with Terry Keane, J. H. Keller, and Andy Mann, 1943 April 8; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2047)
        - Jackman, Harold, 1943 February 3; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2048)
        - LeNoire, Rosetta, 1942 September 11; 11 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2049)
        - Peterson, Dorothy Randolph, and Tom Rutherford, 1943 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2050)
        - Raney, William, and Jane White, 1943 August 9; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2051)
      - Events
        Organized under seven headings for New York City Parades; Opening of the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut; Josephine Baker Day, Harlem, New York City; Carl Van Vechten: His Gifts to Yale. An Exhibition in Honor of His Seventy-fifth Birthday at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut; Wedding of Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at Christ & Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, Westport, Connecticut; Wedding Reception for Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at the Clarence Derwent House, Westport, Connecticut; Party Hosted by Nora Douglas Holt for Singers, James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut; and Performances.
        - New York City Parades
          - Harlem. Peace Mission Movement, Easter parade, 1935 April 21; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2072)
            Roll number IX h.
          - Brooklyn. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1936 August 25; 7 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2073)
            Roll number XLIII j.
          - Brooklyn. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1936 August 25; 10 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2074)
            Roll number I k.
          - Harlem. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1939 August 22; 12 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2075)
            Roll number V q.
          - Harlem. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade. Robinson, Bill, leading the parade, 1939 August 22; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2076)
        - Opening of the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut
          - Barthe, Richmond, with Dorothy Peterson and Ellen Tarry, 1950 January 7; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2077)
          - Gallup, Donald Clifford, with Herman W. Liebert, Chauncey Brewster Tinker, and Carl Van Vechten, 1950 January 7; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2078)
          - Gallup, Donald Clifford, with Herman W. Liebert, Saul Mauriber, and Chauncey Brewster Tinker, 1950 January 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2079)
          - Gallup, Donald Clifford, with Marie Antoinette Burgette Johnson, Dorothy Peterson, and Ellen Tarry, 1950 January 7; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2080)
          - Group, 1950 January 7; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2081)
            Group includes Margaret Bradley Babb, Langston Hughes, Charles Spurgeon Johnson, Marie Antoinette Burgette Johnson, Dorothy Peterson, Helen Channing Pollock, and Ellen Tarry.
          - Johnson, Grace Nail, and Fania Marinoff, 1950 January 7; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2082)
        - Josephine Baker Day, Harlem, New York City
          - Baker, Josephine, in automobile, 1951 May 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2083)
            Roll number XI ii.
          - Hotel Theresa, crowd outside, 1951 May 20; 3 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2084)
          - Hotel Theresa, Skyline Room, luncheon, 1951 May 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2085)
          - Major, Gerri, 1951 May 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2086)
          - Morningside Park, crowd and speakers' stand, 1951 May 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2087)
          - Morningside Park, crowd and speakers' stand, 1951 May 20; 5 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2088)
            Roll number XII ii.
          - Park Palace Ballroom, cocktail dansante, 1951 May 20; 11 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2089)
          - Park Palace Ballroom, cocktail dansante. Major, Gerri, and Lindsay H. White, 1951 May 20; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2090)
        - Carl Van Vechten: His Gifts to Yale. An Exhibition in Honor of His Seventy-fifth Birthday at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut.
          - Adams, Peggy, and Nora Douglas Holt, 1955 June 22; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2091)
            Roll number IX nn.
          - Banks, Richard, and Nora Douglas Holt, 1955 June 22; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2092)
          - Carrington, Glenn, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2093)
          - Holt, Nora Douglas, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 22; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2094)
        - Wedding of Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at Christ & Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, Westport, Connecticut
          - Mauriber, Saul, and Josephine Premice, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2095)
          - Mauriber, Saul, with Josephine Premice as well as a woman and man, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2096)
          - Premice, Josephine, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2097)
          - Premice, Josephine, and a woman, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2098)
        - Wedding Reception for Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at the Clarence Derwent House, Westport, Connecticut
          - Camacho, Leu, with Elaine De Lavallade, Hubert Dilworth, Geoffrey Holder, and Lew Smith, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2099)
            Roll number X nn.
          - Carroll, Diahann, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2100)
          - Carroll, Diahann, and Elwyn M. Chamberlain, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2101)
          - Carroll, Diahann, with Carmen De Lavallade and Saul Mauriber, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2102)
          - Collins, Janet, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2103)
          - De Lavallade, Carmen, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2104)
          - De Lavallade, Carmen, and Geoffrey Holder, 1955 June 26; 4 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2105)
          - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Elaine De Lavallade, Arthur Holder, and Louise de Frense Holder, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2106)
          - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Geoffrey Holder, and Lucille Lortel, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2107)
          - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Geoffrey Holder, Fania Marinoff, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2108)
          - Johnson, Louis, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2109)
          - Johnson, Louis, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2110)
          - Major, Gerri, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2111)
          - Premice, Josephine, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2112)
          - Wedding cake, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2113)
        - Party Hosted by Nora Douglas Holt for Singers, James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut
          - Allen, Betty, with Carol Brice and Lawrence Winters, 1959 September 9; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2114)
          - Bonds, Margaret, with Mrs. Jeffers and Charlotte Holloman, 1959 September 9; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2115)
          - Brice, Eugene, and Charlotte Holloman, 1959 September 9; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2116)
          - Holt, Nora, with Margaret Tynes and William Warfield, 1959 September 9; 2 photographic prints (Box 111, Folder 2117)
          - Marinoff, Fania, and William Warfield, 1959 September 9; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2118)
          - Moore, Leon, and his sister, 1959 September 9; 1 photographic print (Box 111, Folder 2119)
        - Performances
          - Hall, Adelaide, at the Palace Theatre, New York City, 1932 July 25; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2052)
            Roll number Ss.
          - Robeson, Paul, as Joe, during a performance of Showboat, musical with music by Jerome Kern and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, at the Casino Theatre, 1932 August 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2053)
            Roll number Uu.
          - As Thousands Cheer, musical revue by with music and lyrics by Irving Berlin and book by Moss Hart. Waters, Ethel, singing "Heat Wave Hits New York" during a performance at the Music Box Theatre, 1933 September 12; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2054)
            Roll number XXIII d.
          - As Thousands Cheer, musical revue by with music and lyrics by Irving Berlin and book by Moss Hart. Waters, Ethel, singing "To Be Or Not To Be" with Hamtree Harrington during a performance at the Music Box Theatre, 1933 September 12; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2055)
          - Davis, Sammy, Jr., at a National Urban League benefit at Birdland, Manhattan, New York City, 1956 June 10; 4 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2056)
            Roll number I pp.
      - Places
        Arranged alphabetically.
        - Barbados. Informal portrait of a woman, 1951 March 3; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2057)
          Roll number I ii.
        - New York City. Flushing Meadows-Corona Park. New York World's Fair. Boy Scouts, 1939 June 29; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2058)
          Roll number XIV p.
        - New York City. Manhattan. American Museum of Natural History. Equestrian Statue of Theodore Roosevelt, sculpture by James Earle Fraser, 1944 June 10; 4 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2059)
        - New York City. Manhattan. Broadway Avenue. Broadside outside the Empire Theatre for Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1939 May 8; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2060)
          Roll number XXII o.
        - New York City. Manhattan. Broadway Avenue. Cast list outside the Empire Theatre Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1938 December 26; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2061)
        - New York City. Manhattan. Central Park. USS Maine National Monument. View of boys, 1937 August 25; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2062)
          Roll number VII L.
          Identified on recto as "Boys in Columbus Circle."
        - New York City. Manhattan. Central Park. USS Maine National Monument. Views of boys in the fountain, 1937 August 12; 9 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2063)
          Roll number VI L.
        - New York City. Manhattan. Central Park. USS Maine National Monument. Views of boys in the fountain, 1937 September 3; 6 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2064)
          Roll number X L.
          Identified by Library staff on recto as " Maine Monument Series."
        - New York City. Manhattan. Fifth Avenue, side street. View of a road construction worker, 1939 April 3; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2065)
          Roll number XV o.
          Location identified on recto as "off Sixth Avenue."
        - New York City. Manhattan. Sixth Avenue. View of a road construction worker, 1938 June 25; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2066)
        - New York City. Manhattan. Sixth Avenue. View of a subway construction worker, 1937 August 25; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2067)
        - New York. Wantagh. Jones Beach State Park. West Bath House pool, 1939 August 7; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2068)
          Roll number I q.
          Inscription on one print misidentifies the date as June 7, 1939.
        - Pennsylvania. Philadelphia. North 25th Street and Ridge Avenue. James Weldon Johnson Homes, 1942 August 14; 1 photographic print (Box 110, Folder 2069)
          Roll number XXI w.
        - Trinidad and Tobago. Port of Spain. Views, 1951 March 2; 3 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2070)
          Roll number XXV hh.
        - United States Virgin Islands. Saint Thomas. Move theater, 1951 February 28; 2 photographic prints (Box 110, Folder 2071)
          Roll number XXIV hh.
      - Artwork
        Arranged alphabetically by surname of the artist.
        - Barthé, Richmond. Feral Benga, 1935, sculpture, 1937 July 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 112, Folder 2120)
        - Barthé, Richmond. Julius, circa 1940, sculpture, 1940 October 23; 6 photographic prints (Box 112, Folder 2121)
          Roll number XII s.
          Bust depicts Julius Perkins, Jr.